Aizaz Jamil

Technologies

HTML, Pug CSS3, Sass/Scss/Less Bootstrap 3,4 **JavaScript** iQuery Github React Js (Beginner) PSD to HTML WordPress Responsive Design **Photoshop** HTML Email

Software

Visual Studio Code Sublime Text Atom

Education

Govt. College Asghar Mall (ICS) Computer Science

Personal

Email: aizaz-jamil28@outlook.com

Mobile: +92 348 5552127

Status: Single

Address: H1-347 Muslim Town Kurri Road Sadigabad, Rawalpindi,

Pakistan

CNIC No: 37402-6597009-3

Information

Urdu English

Training Program

React Js

Summary

I am a front end developer. I have 2+ years' experience in Front End Technologies. I am a self-learner and motivate person, I can face web related stuffs alone or working together with team members, Also I am Front End Developer for Web. I hope my positive attitude is do and make something

Professional Experience

AiiMS - Discover Your Uniqueness

Front-End Developer

09/2019 - Present

- Used HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap3/4, JavaScript, JQuery, Sass/Scss, Flexbox, Css Grid and Js Libraries.
- Converts PSDs into hand-coded HTML/CSS.
- Strong knowledge of front-end technologies including HTML5, JQuery, Bootstrap, CSS3, JavaScript.
- Created and implemented a custom CSS flexbox system, with CSS media queries for mobile responsiveness.
- Worked on cross-browser compatibility.

Digital Poin8

Front-End Developer

08/2019 - Present

- Used HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap3/4, JavaScript, JQuery, Sass/Scss, PostCss, WordPress and Js Libraries.
- Converts PSDs into hand-coded HTML/CSS.
- Strong knowledge of front-end technologies including HTML5, JQuery, Bootstrap, CSS3, JavaScript and WordPress
- Created and implemented a custom CSS flexbox system, with CSS media queries for mobile responsiveness.
- Worked on cross-browser compatibility.

Ark Techno Solutions

Front-End Developer

12/2017 - 07/2019

- Used HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap3/4, JavaScript, JQuery, Sass/Scss, PostCss and Js Libraries.
- Converts PSDs into hand-coded HTML/CSS.
- Strong knowledge of front-end technologies including HTML5, JQuery, Bootstrap, CSS3, JavaScript.
- Created and implemented a custom CSS flexbox system, with CSS media queries for mobile responsiveness.
- Worked on cross-browser compatibility.